heels.com 2017-05-27

# Women's Shoes, Dress Shoes, Evening Shoes, Guess Shoes, Jessica Simpson Shoes, LAMB Shoes, High Heels, Heels.com

## Heels.com Privacy Policy

We recognize that making purchases at Heels.com or any website requires a high level of trust. We value your trust and confidence and vow to protect your privacy and the security of all personal information you provide to us. We do not and will not rent, sale, or loan your personal information to anyone.

It is our goal to create a long term relationship with you, our customer. To accomplish this we feel it is essential for us to communicate the information we are collecting and how we intend on using it to create a better shopping experience.

### Use of Cookies

When you visit Heels.com your computer will be assigned a unique identifiable text file to be stored within your hard drive. Most websites today do this to identify the visitors. The purpose of this cookie is to identify you when you visit our site so we can enhance your online shopping experience. You can choose to shop Heels.com without cookies, but you will not be able to take advantage of certain features on the site. We also collect source code by reading parameters embedded in the URL of the link that you clicked onto our site. We do not and will not rent, sale, or loan your personal information to anyone.

### Sharing of Information

To provide you with the best shopping experience at Heels.com, we may share some anonymous information about your browsing history while you have been on our site. This information is not personally identifiable, and generally includes products you have viewed and pages you have visited at Heels.com. We gather this information by utilizing Web Beacons (also called tracking pixels on some instances), which is a graphic image or small string of code, that is included on our pages to facilitate communication and data exchange with our approved Third Parties. Web beacons are generally used by web sites for recording web site traffic, customer preferences, advertising effectiveness, and general auditing. We use this information to generate suggested products you may be interested in, as well as other services to enhance your shopping experience. We may be required to share this information with Third Parties that we have approved as secure, in order to provide these Third Parties with information about your browsing history while visiting Heels.com. This information will never be used to identify you personally, and contains no identifiable information about you or your purchases.

### Live Chat

Heels.com has partnered with vee24 to provide our customers with a live, video chat service directly with our customer service experts. vee24 is a leading provider of video engagement technology that facilitates real-time sales and customer services for companies doing business on the Internet. During the engagement, Heels.com customers enter into a live question and answer session with an operator either by text chat or live video call. We maintain dialogue transcripts of these chats. After the chat, we ask Heels.com customers to fill out an exit survey in order to obtain valuable feedback about the levels of our service. Filling out the exit survey is completely voluntary. Moreover, all personal data is only collected if you voluntarily supply it, e.g. when completing a contact us form. If during the live engagement the individual chooses to enter personal or business data (email addresses, names, addresses), the disclosure of such data is done so by the user on a voluntary basis. Such information is not passed to any third parties or used for any other purpose(s) than that/those requested by the customer. The vee24 system gives users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include opting not to engage in video call or chat sessions.

### Information Collection

We log browser information (e.g. Internet Protocol addresses and browser types) to help diagnose problems with our server, gather broad demographic information and administer our site. By choosing to engage in a chat or video call and use the services, the user consents to such logging and processing of IP address.

### Recording of Communications

Heels.com aims to offer you the best possible help and advice in the context of your visit to our page. As part of the live engagement you have the option to choose (by pressing the appropriate buttons) different communication channels. If you have chosen an engagement via voice or video communications, a recording of that communication does not take place at any time and therefore no video or voice data is either captured or stored. You have the option at any time to terminate the conversation by pressing the appropriate button.

### Social Networking

Heels.com utilizes many social sharing technologies offered by Facebook, including allowing our customers to “Like” any of our products on our web store through the use of the Facebook “Like” button on Heels.com product pages. Users should be aware that by ‘Liking’ a product on Heels.com using the Facebook ‘Like’ Button, that user agrees to allow Heels.com to list their name, photo, and any other ‘Everyone’, publicly viewable information the user has allowed to be accessed on their Facebook Profile. The use of the ‘Like’ button may also publish the product photo, description, and link back to the Heels.com page on the users Facebook ‘Wall’. This information may be viewable to your Facebook network, depending on your privacy settings. By using the Facebook ‘Like’ button on a Heels.com product page, you agree to allow us to use that information, and any associated ‘Everyone’ publicly accessible information from your Facebook profile, including your name, photo, and any comments you attach to your ‘Like’ wall posting, for both commercial and non-commercial uses, including but not limited to promotions or advertising for Heels.com.

We reserve the right to change or amend our privacy policy at any time.

If you have any question concerning our policy please contact us at

Heels.com  
550 S. Caldwell St.  
17th Floor  
Charlotte, NC 28202  
(866) 33-HEELS
